ebooki.cc 2018-12-29

# Ebooki

### Welcome to Ebooki

**Privacy policy**

This Privacy Statement explains our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of certain information, including your personal information, by the Provider.

We recognize that your privacy is very important to you and that it is your right to control your personal information. We know that providing personal information is an act of trust and we take that trust seriously. We will never sell, rent or disclose your personal information, including your email address, to third parties without your consent. Unless you give us your specific consent to act otherwise, the following policies will govern how we handle the personal information you provide us.

**1\. Consent to the privacy policy**

By continuing to use the Provider Services, you accept this Privacy Policy. This is our complete and exclusive Privacy Policy, and it replaces any previous version. This Privacy Policy is part of and must be read together with our Terms and Conditions of Use.

**2\. Collection of personal identification information**

  * While using the Services, we ask that you provide us with certain personally identifiable information that may be used to contact you or identify you and manage your account ("Personal Information", "Personally Identifiable Information"). Personal information may include, but is not limited to, your name, telephone number, credit card or other billing information, email address and home and business postal addresses.
  * As you use the Services, our servers automatically record the information that the browser sends each time it points to a website or online service ("Registration Data"). The registration data may include, among others, the Internet Protocol address of your computer, the type of browser, the web page you were visiting before arriving at one of the Sites and the information you search on a Site.

**3\. Use of information**

  * Payment information. We only use payment information, such as credit card numbers, as necessary to complete a particular transaction or to fulfill a service and to prevent abuse.
  * Other information. We use the other information we collect about you to establish and improve our relationship and help you achieve a first level experience. Our use of this information includes the following general purposes:

    * contact you;
    * customize the content and the advertising you see;
    * fulfilling your requests for products or services;
    * identify the content you share when you use our services;
    * improve them;
    * conduct research;
    * compile aggregate data for internal and external business purposes;
    * prevent potentially illegal activities;
    * protect our rights;
    * other uses in accordance with our Terms and Conditions of Use;
    * and for any other purpose that may have been disclosed to you at the time we collect your information.

  * Recommendations and publicity. We (and the service providers acting on our behalf) may use your information, including the use of our Services, to provide recommendations and advertisements on our Services and on other websites.
  * Promotional communications: We can use your information to:

    * provide you with promotional information about our services and other offers that may interest you;
    * provide you with information or offers related to our Services on behalf of our business partners.

**4\. Exchange of information and dissemination**

We are committed to protecting your personal information. We will not disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent, except:

  * where the law requires us to disclose information to third parties;
  * where the disclosure is necessary for the performance of our operations (for example, mail delivery, hosting services, fraud protection and payment of your account);
  * If we buy or sell subsidiaries or business units, that is, in relation to a corporate transaction, such as a sale, merger, consolidation or sale of assets, or an internal reorganization, or in the unlikely event of an insolvency. If said transaction or event requires the transfer of customer information, said information would be one of the transferred assets, but would remain subject to the commitments established in any pre-existing or equivalent Privacy Policy.

We may also share your personal information with third parties (ie, agents or subcontractors) specifically contracted by us to provide us with services, in which case we will require those parties to keep that information confidential and secure and to use it only for the purpose of providing the services. specified.

We also provide analysis of our clients together with potential partners, advertisers, distributors and other third parties. We do this so that we and our business partners can understand it better, so we can continue to offer you first class services. We can also disclose, anonymously, literal statements made by our clients. At no time, however, will we disclose personal information about specific clients.

The linked websites are not under our control and we are not responsible for the conduct of the companies linked to our website. Before disclosing your personal information on any other website, we advise you to examine its terms, use and privacy policy.

All of our members can review, update, correct or delete personal information in their registration profile by logging into their account and changing the user preferences associated with it. If you completely remove all that information, your account may be disabled. We may keep an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes.

**5\. Cookies**

What is a cookie?

  * Cookies are text files that contain small amounts of information that are downloaded to your personal computer, mobile device or other device when you visit a website. The cookies are sent to the origin website at each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognizes that cookie. Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognize a user's device.
  * Permanent cookies: these cookies remain on a user's device during the period of time specified in the cookie. They are activated every time the user visits the website that created that particular cookie.
  * Session cookies: these cookies allow website operators to link the actions of a user during a browser session. A browser session starts when a user opens the browser window and ends when they close the browser window. Session cookies are created temporarily. Once you close the browser, all session cookies will be deleted.
  * Cookies do many different jobs, such as allowing you to navigate between pages efficiently, remember your preferences and, in general, improve the user experience. They can also help ensure that the ads you see online are more relevant to you and your interests.

Below is a list of all the cookies that can be used on the website by category.

  * Strictly necessary cookies: these cookies enable the services you have specifically requested. For those types of cookies that are strictly necessary, consent is not required. These cookies are essential to allow you to move around the website and use its functions, such as access to secure areas of the website. Without these services of cookies that you have requested, the service can not be provided.
  * Performance cookies: these cookies collect anonymous information on the pages visited. By using the website, you accept that we can place this type of cookies on your device. These cookies collect information about how visitors use the website, for example, which pages visitors visit most often and if they receive error messages from web pages. These cookies do not collect information that identifies a visitor. All information collected by these cookies is anonymous. It is only used to improve the functioning of the website.
  * Functionality cookies: these cookies remember the choices you make to improve your experience. By using the website, you accept that we can place this type of cookies on your device. These cookies allow the website to remember the choices made (such as your user name, language or the region in which it is located) and provide improved and more personal characteristics. These cookies can also be used to remember the changes you have made in the size of the text, the fonts and other parts of the web pages that you can customize. They can also be used to provide the services you requested, such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information that these cookies collect can be anonymous and they can not track your browsing activity on other websites.
  * Orientation or advertising cookies: these cookies collect information about your browsing habits to make relevant advertising for you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an ad and to help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are usually placed by ad networks with our permission. Remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organizations, such as advertisers. Very often, the orientation or advertising cookies will be linked to the functionality of the site provided by the other organization.

**6\. Online behavioral advertising and privacy**

The Internet advertising industry has produced an online behavioral advertising and privacy guide that can be found at [http://youronlinechoices.eu](http://youronlinechoices.eu/). The guide contains an explanation of the IAB self-regulation scheme to allow you more control of the advertising you see.

Use browser settings to manage cookies:

  * The Help menu in the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to make the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable them altogether. You can also disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the plug-in's settings or by visiting its manufacturer's website.
  * However, as cookies allow you to take advantage of some of the essential features of the website, we recommend that you leave them activated. For example, if you block or reject cookies, you can not use any of our products and services that require you to log in. If you leave cookies activated, remember to log out when using a shared device.

**7\. Changes and updates**

We may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy and we will notify you of these changes by posting them on the Website. We recommend that you revisit this Privacy Policy regularly. If we are going to use Personal Information in a manner materially different from that established at the time of collection, we will notify you by posting a notice in our Services. You can determine when this Privacy Policy was last updated by consulting the date at the end of this Privacy Policy. "This Privacy Policy was last modified and becomes effective as of."

**8\. Contact**

Questions, comments and requests related to this Privacy Policy are welcome and should be directed to our support email: support@ebooki.cc

This Privacy Policy was modified for the last time and becomes effective on June 1, 2018.
